{"data":[{"question":"The thieves had to throw away all that ___ them while fleeing.","a":"didn't belong to","b":"weren't belonged to","c":"hadn't been belonged to","d":"weren't belonging to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"had to\") + active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't be worried. Two doctors ___.","a":"were sent for","b":"have sent for","c":"have been sent for","d":"will send for","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense:(to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now) + passive voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Engines ___ by electricity.","a":"are made run","b":"make to run","c":"are made to run","d":"were made running","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (use to talk about general fact) \n- Make sbd do sth \n- Passive: be made to verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"This museum ___ within two years.","a":"had been completed","b":"is completed","c":"will complete","d":"will be completed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple future tense (express the idea of a general prediction about the future) + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The feather overcoat ___ at a high price last winter.","a":"was sold","b":"sold","c":"had sold","d":"has been sold","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + passive voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"How are things getting on? \"All that can be done ___ \"","a":"have been done","b":"has been done","c":"have done","d":"has done","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: (We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now) + Passive vocie ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"It was the shortest film I had ever seen. It only ___ one hour.","a":"remained","b":"kept","c":"finished","d":"lasted","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Last: to continue for a particular length of time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Jack is ___ a yellow jacket today.","a":"put on","b":"having","c":"dressed","d":"wearing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Wear: to have something such as clothes, shoes, or jewellery on your body \n- Present continuous tense (to express the idea that something is happening now, at this very moment. It can also be used to show that something is not happening now) + active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The child is not old enough to ___ itself.","a":"wear","b":"dress","c":"have on","d":"put on","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Dress = put on clothes: to put clothes on yourself or someone else","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The city's subway ___ more passengers than the buses.","a":"carries","b":"brings","c":"fetches","d":"sends","answer":"1","explain":"- Carry: if a vehicle someone or something somewhere, it take them there","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}